<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Converter on YoSQL</title><link>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/converter/</link><description>Recent content in Converter on YoSQL</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/converter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>defaultConverter</title><link>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/converter/defaultconverter/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/converter/defaultconverter/</guid><description>The default converter to use, if no other is specified on a query itself.
Configuration Options Related Options generateMapConverter: Whether the ToMap converter should be generated. mapConverterAlias: The name of the alias referencing the ToMap converter. mapConverterClass: The fully-qualified class name of the ToMap converter. mapConverterMethod: The name of the method to generate/call in the ToMap converter. rowConverters: The converters configured by the user. Tooling Ant In order to use YoSQL together with Ant, take a look at the tooling documentation for Ant.</description></item><item><title>generateMapConverter</title><link>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/converter/generatemapconverter/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/converter/generatemapconverter/</guid><description>Whether the ToMap converter should be generated.
Configuration Options Related Options defaultConverter: The default converter to use, if no other is specified on a query itself. mapConverterAlias: The name of the alias referencing the ToMap converter. mapConverterClass: The fully-qualified class name of the ToMap converter. mapConverterMethod: The name of the method to generate/call in the ToMap converter. rowConverters: The converters configured by the user. Tooling Ant In order to use YoSQL together with Ant, take a look at the tooling documentation for Ant.</description></item><item><title>mapConverterAlias</title><link>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/converter/mapconverteralias/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/converter/mapconverteralias/</guid><description>The name of the alias referencing the ToMap converter.
Configuration Options Related Options defaultConverter: The default converter to use, if no other is specified on a query itself. generateMapConverter: Whether the ToMap converter should be generated. mapConverterClass: The fully-qualified class name of the ToMap converter. mapConverterMethod: The name of the method to generate/call in the ToMap converter. rowConverters: The converters configured by the user. Tooling Ant In order to use YoSQL together with Ant, take a look at the tooling documentation for Ant.</description></item><item><title>mapConverterClass</title><link>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/converter/mapconverterclass/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/converter/mapconverterclass/</guid><description>The fully-qualified class name of the ToMap converter.
Configuration Options Related Options defaultConverter: The default converter to use, if no other is specified on a query itself. generateMapConverter: Whether the ToMap converter should be generated. mapConverterAlias: The name of the alias referencing the ToMap converter. mapConverterMethod: The name of the method to generate/call in the ToMap converter. rowConverters: The converters configured by the user. Tooling Ant In order to use YoSQL together with Ant, take a look at the tooling documentation for Ant.</description></item><item><title>mapConverterMethod</title><link>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/converter/mapconvertermethod/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/converter/mapconvertermethod/</guid><description>The name of the method to generate/call in the ToMap converter.
Configuration Options Related Options defaultConverter: The default converter to use, if no other is specified on a query itself. generateMapConverter: Whether the ToMap converter should be generated. mapConverterAlias: The name of the alias referencing the ToMap converter. mapConverterClass: The fully-qualified class name of the ToMap converter. rowConverters: The converters configured by the user. Tooling Ant In order to use YoSQL together with Ant, take a look at the tooling documentation for Ant.</description></item><item><title>rowConverters</title><link>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/converter/rowconverters/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/converter/rowconverters/</guid><description>The converters configured by the user.
Configuration Options Related Options defaultConverter: The default converter to use, if no other is specified on a query itself. generateMapConverter: Whether the ToMap converter should be generated. mapConverterAlias: The name of the alias referencing the ToMap converter. mapConverterClass: The fully-qualified class name of the ToMap converter. mapConverterMethod: The name of the method to generate/call in the ToMap converter. Tooling Ant In order to use YoSQL together with Ant, take a look at the tooling documentation for Ant.</description></item></channel></rss>