<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Java on YoSQL</title><link>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/java/</link><description>Recent content in Java on YoSQL</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/java/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>apiVersion</title><link>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/java/apiversion/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/java/apiversion/</guid><description>Controls the Java SDK API version to use in generated code.
Configuration Options Option: &amp;lsquo;17&amp;rsquo; The default value of the apiVersion configuration option is 17. It is updated alongside the minimum Java version required by YoSQL.
Option: &amp;lsquo;11&amp;rsquo; Changing the apiVersion configuration option to 11 will allow generated code to use Java APIs up until version 11 (including).
Related Options useFinalClasses: Controls whether classes are declared as final in generated code.</description></item><item><title>useFinalClasses</title><link>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/java/usefinalclasses/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/java/usefinalclasses/</guid><description>Controls whether classes are declared as final in generated code.
Configuration Options Option: &amp;rsquo;true' The default value of the useFinalClasses configuration option is true which enables the use of final for classes.
Option: &amp;lsquo;false&amp;rsquo; Changing the useFinalClasses configuration option to false disables the use of final for classes.
Related Options apiVersion: Controls the Java SDK API version to use in generated code. useFinalFields: Controls whether fields are declared as final in generated code.</description></item><item><title>useFinalFields</title><link>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/java/usefinalfields/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/java/usefinalfields/</guid><description>Controls whether fields are declared as final in generated code.
Configuration Options Option: &amp;rsquo;true' The default value of the useFinalFields configuration option is true which enables the use of final for fields.
Option: &amp;lsquo;false&amp;rsquo; Changing the useFinalFields configuration option to false disables the use of final for fields.
Related Options apiVersion: Controls the Java SDK API version to use in generated code. useFinalClasses: Controls whether classes are declared as final in generated code.</description></item><item><title>useFinalMethods</title><link>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/java/usefinalmethods/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/java/usefinalmethods/</guid><description>Controls whether methods are declared as final in generated code.
Configuration Options Option: &amp;rsquo;true' The default value of the useFinalMethods configuration option is true which enables the use of final for methods.
Option: &amp;lsquo;false&amp;rsquo; Changing the useFinalMethods configuration option to false disables the use of final for methods.
Related Options apiVersion: Controls the Java SDK API version to use in generated code. useFinalClasses: Controls whether classes are declared as final in generated code.</description></item><item><title>useFinalParameters</title><link>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/java/usefinalparameters/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/java/usefinalparameters/</guid><description>Controls whether parameters are declared as final in generated code.
Configuration Options Option: &amp;rsquo;true' The default value of the useFinalParameters configuration option is true which enables the use of final for parameters.
Option: &amp;lsquo;false&amp;rsquo; Changing the useFinalParameters configuration option to false disables the use of final for parameters.
Related Options apiVersion: Controls the Java SDK API version to use in generated code. useFinalClasses: Controls whether classes are declared as final in generated code.</description></item><item><title>useFinalVariables</title><link>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/java/usefinalvariables/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/java/usefinalvariables/</guid><description>Controls whether variables are declared as final in generated code.
Configuration Options Option: &amp;rsquo;true' The default value of the useFinalVariables configuration option is true which enables the use of final for variables.
Option: &amp;lsquo;false&amp;rsquo; Changing the useFinalVariables configuration option to false disables the use of final for variables.
Related Options apiVersion: Controls the Java SDK API version to use in generated code. useFinalClasses: Controls whether classes are declared as final in generated code.</description></item><item><title>useSealedInterfaces</title><link>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/java/usesealedinterfaces/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/java/usesealedinterfaces/</guid><description>Controls whether interfaces should be sealed
Configuration Options Option: &amp;lsquo;false&amp;rsquo; The default value of the useSealedInterfaces configuration option is false which disables sealing interfaces in generated code.
Option: &amp;rsquo;true' Changing the useSealedInterfaces configuration option to true enables sealing interfaces in generated code.
Related Options apiVersion: Controls the Java SDK API version to use in generated code. useFinalClasses: Controls whether classes are declared as final in generated code. useFinalFields: Controls whether fields are declared as final in generated code.</description></item><item><title>useTextBlocks</title><link>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/java/usetextblocks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/java/usetextblocks/</guid><description>Controls the usage of text blocks in generated code.
Configuration Options Option: &amp;rsquo;true' The default value of the useTextBlocks configuration option is true which enables the use of text blocks in generated code.
Option: &amp;lsquo;false&amp;rsquo; Changing the useTextBlocks configuration option to false disables the use of text blocks in generated code.
Related Options apiVersion: Controls the Java SDK API version to use in generated code. useFinalClasses: Controls whether classes are declared as final in generated code.</description></item><item><title>useVar</title><link>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/java/usevar/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yosql.projects.metio.wtf/configuration/java/usevar/</guid><description>Controls the usage of the &amp;lsquo;var&amp;rsquo; keyword in generated code.
Configuration Options Option: &amp;rsquo;true&amp;rsquo; The default value of the useVar configuration option is true which enables the use of var in generated code.
Option: &amp;lsquo;false&amp;rsquo; Changing the useVar configuration option to false disables the use of var in generated code.
Related Options apiVersion: Controls the Java SDK API version to use in generated code. useFinalClasses: Controls whether classes are declared as final in generated code.</description></item></channel></rss>